mlgpro.com 2014-10-13

# MLG Account Management - MLG - Major League Gaming

**_Major League Gaming Privacy Policy_**

Welcome and thank you for visiting the MLG network of websites, an interactive online service operated by Major League Gaming, Inc. (“Major League Gaming” or “MLG”). Major League Gaming has posted this privacy policy in order to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy. This privacy policy applies to all of the websites offered by Major League Gaming (collectively, the “Services”), including [mlgpro.com](http://mlgpro.com/), [gamebattles.com](http://gamebattles.com/), [majorleaguegaming.com](http://majorleaguegaming.com/), [mlg.tv](http://mlg.tv/), and [gotfrag.com](http://gotfrag.com/). The following discloses Major League Gaming’s online information collection and use practices and the choices you can make about the way we use and share such information.

BY ACCESSING AND USING THE SERVICES, YOU ACCEPT, WITHOUT LIMITATION OR QUALIFICATION, THIS PRIVACY POLICY, SO PLEASE TAKE THE TIME TO READ THIS POLICY AND UNDERSTAND HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.  PLEASE NOTE THAT OUR ONLINE INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE PRACTICES MAY DIFFER FROM OUR PRACTICES REGARDING INFORMATION OBTAINED OFFLINE. IF YOU DO NOT ACCEPT THIS PRIVACY POLICY IN ITS ENTIRETY, YOU MAY NOT USE THE SERVICES.

This privacy policy may change from time to time.  It is important that you check this privacy policy periodically.  Each version of this privacy policy will be identified at the bottom of the page by its effective date.

**The Personal Information We Collect.**  When using our Services or registering for the Website, you may be asked to provide, or you may choose to upload, certain personally identifiable information about yourself ( _i.e._ information that can directly identify you or indicate where you might be contacted) (hereinafter referred to as "Personal Information").

For example, you can order products, enter competitions, participate in surveys, vote in polls, subscribe to a service (like our newsletter) or participate in a chat room, message board or forum. The types of Personal Information that may be collected through your participation in the Services may include: name, address, age, date of birth, gender, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, Xbox LIVE account information, PlayStation Network account information and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs and services. Sometimes you can submit Personal Information about other people. For example, you might submit a person's name and e-mail address to send an electronic greeting card and, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to a friend, you might submit the friend's name and address. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages may include: recipient's name, address, age, date of birth, e-mail address, gender and telephone number. 

In addition, you may choose to include Personal Information in your MLG public profile.  For example, you may include information such as your name, address, age, date of birth, gender, contact information, what video games you play, your Xbox LIVE and/or PlayStation Network account name and what video game consoles you own.  By sharing such information on your MLG public profile, you acknowledge that others may view and access such information from your public profile.

We collect this Personal Information so we can better understand your interests and tailor the Services to suit you better.  In any event, you may always decline to submit Personal Information to any of our Services, in which case we may not be able to provide those Services to you.  

**How We Use Your Personal Information.**  
We will use the Personal Information you provide online for the purpose(s) you have submitted. Examples of us using your Personal Information for the purpose(s) submitted include if you buy a game, sending to you the game in the mail or, if you have won a contest, sending to you an e-mail notification that you have won. In addition, we may send to you an e-mail offering products or services which we think may interest you, or asking you to participate in a survey. For example, we may send to you an e-mail regarding special merchandise offers and announcements about products or services offered by Major League Gaming. We may also contact you offline. For example, when you provide your mailing address, Major League Gaming may send to you in the mail special offers, promotions and catalogs, which we think may be of interest to you. If you want us to stop using the Personal Information you provided in these ways, please send an e-mail to remove@mlgpro.com.  

**How We Share Your Personal Information.**  
Unless disclosed at time of collection, we will not share the Personal Information you provide with anyone not affiliated with Major League Gaming except (a) if it is for the purpose(s) you provided the information; (b) with your opt-in or opt-out consent; (c) with other persons or companies with whom we contract with to carry out or fulfill internal Services operations (for example, hosting part of the Website) or our business activities (for example, sending out a product or a promotional item that you have requested on the Website); and/or (d) if required by courts, government authorities and other regulatory agencies, and to the extent required to permit us to investigate any potential violations of any law, rule, regulation, MLG rules or policies, rights of third parties, or to investigate any other potentially improper conduct.

One example of where we may share your Personal Information for the purpose submitted is if you enter a contest, sweepstakes or promotion sponsored by or co-sponsored by a non-affiliated third party.  Based on our agreement with them, these third parties may obtain Personal Information that you voluntarily submit to participate in the contest, sweepstakes, or promotion. We have no control over the use of this information by these companies.

When your consent is required for use of Personal Information that is not otherwise authorized by this privacy policy, we will seek to obtain your consent at the place where the information is collected either by an “opt-in” or “opt-out” method, or by other means (such as sending to you an e-mail). We may share Personal Information with our affiliated companies, including companies owned directly or indirectly by Major League Gaming, or under common ownership. Any of these companies may use and further share this information in the same ways we do.

As noted above, with your opt-in or opt-out consent, we may share the Personal Information you provide online with companies not affiliated with us ( _i.e._ third party companies) who want to market products or services to you or to ask you questions, both online and offline. If you want us to stop sharing your Personal Information with these companies, contact us at [remove@mlgpro.com](mailto:remove@mlgpro.com).  You may also visit http://www.networkadvertising.org for more information on how to opt-out of the use of technologies for the delivery of behavioral advertising.  If you consent to receiving communications from non-affiliated companies, you may need to communicate with them directly if you later decide that you no longer wish to receive their communications or if you wish to change any data you provided online. In this instance, any changes or amendments to your Personal Information must be given directly to each company who communicates with you as these changes, amendments and/or deletions will not be exchanged between us and non-affiliated companies. We cannot guarantee how these non-affiliated companies will use your Personal Information.

Please note that we reserve the right to access or disclose your Personal Information and other information we gather as required by courts, government authorities or other regulatory agencies and to the extent required to permit us to investigate suspected fraud, harassment or other violations of any law, rule or regulation, MLG rules or policies, or rights of third parties or to investigate any suspected conduct which we deem improper. 

**Use and Disclosure of Non-Personally Identifiable Information.**

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information, such as pages viewed, advertisements clicked, browser type ( _e.g._ , Firefox, Internet Explorer, Chrome), operating system ( _e.g._ , Windows or Mac OS) and other data.

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our Services and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience.  We may aggregate such information collected in a manner that does not identify any individual (“Aggregate Information”) to improve and enhance your experience with the Services and for our market research and advertising activities.  For example, we may share Aggregate Information with affiliated and unaffiliated third parties, such as business partners, advertisers, ad networks, manufacturers, distributors and retailers, in an aggregate, anonymous form, which means that the shared information will not contain nor be linked to any Personal Information.  

**Other Web Sites.** Our Services may contain links to other web sites whose information and privacy practices may be different than ours. We encourage you to be aware that when you leave our Websites, or surf the Internet, that you read the privacy statement of each and every web site you visit because we have no control over information that is submitted or collected by other sites.  We do not endorse, screen, or approve, and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other web sites.

**Cookies.**  
“Cookies” are pieces of information that may be placed on your computer by a web site for purposes of facilitating and enhancing your communication and interaction with the web site. Many web sites use cookies for these purposes.  When you use our Services, we may send one or more cookies to your computer or other device that uniquely identifies your browser.  We use such cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences, improving ad selection, measuring aggregate, anonymous data for usage and traffic of our Services, and tracking the frequency and placement of advertisements.

You may stop or restrict the placement of cookies on your computer or flush them from your browser by adjusting your web browser preferences, in which case you may still use our Services, but certain MLG features and services may not function properly.  For example, you may need to re-register with us every time you visit our Website in order to participate in certain promotions and other offers.

**Clickstream Data.**  
As you use the Internet, a trail of electronic information is left at each web site you visit. This information, which is sometimes referred to as “clickstream data,” can be collected and stored by a web site’s server. Clickstream data can reveal the type of computer and browser you use and the address of the web site from which you linked to our Services. We may use clickstream data as a form of non-personally identifiable information to anonymously determine how much time visitors spend on each page of our Website, how visitors navigate throughout the Website and how we may tailor our web pages to better meet the needs of visitors.

**Web Beacons.**

Our Services may also use web beacon technology to help track usage. Web beacons (also called single pixel gifs or action tags) allow Major League Gaming to track page viewing counts and patterns, which we use to focus and tailor future content development and otherwise measure and improve the performance of the Services.

At times, some of the advertisers on our Services and their ad service providers set cookies and web beacons when you click their advertisements. While we use cookies and web beacons in other parts of the Services (as discussed above), cookies and web beacons received with banner ads are collected by those advertisers and their ad service providers. The advertiser’s privacy policy and/or that of its service provider governs the use of this information and Major League Gaming is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other companies.

**Supplementing Information.**

From time to time we may supplement information you give us with information from other sources, such as information validating your address. Thus, information we obtain through the Services may be intermingled with and used in conjunction with information obtained through sources other than the Services, including both offline and online sources.

**Discussions and Community Tools.**

We may, from time to time, make chat rooms, message boards, forums, blogs, news groups and other publicly accessible forums and community tools available to you. You should be aware that Personal Information you post to chat rooms, message boards, forums, blogs, news groups or other publicly accessible forums and community tools may be viewed and used by anyone with access to such forums.  We are unable to control such uses of your Personal Information, and by using the Services you assume the risk that the Personal Information provided by you may be viewed and used by third parties.

From time to time, we may use the content you write (including your name or screen name if you post it) for promotional purposes, in e-mail newsletters or elsewhere, and by using the Services, including without limitation these chat rooms, forums, message boards, news groups, and other community tools, and you agree that we may do so. Accordingly, you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your Personal Information in these areas, since anyone - not just us - may use publicly posted information.

**Our Commitment to Security.**  
The security of your Personal Information is very important to us, and we have put in place reasonable physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard and help protect your Personal Information.

However, because no computer system or information can ever be fully protected against every possible hazard, and thus, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and us or information stored on our Services or our servers will be completely free from unauthorized access, destruction, misuse, modification and improper disclosure by third parties such as hackers. Your use of the Services demonstrates your assumption of these risks.

**International Users.**  
If you are accessing our Services from a location outside of the United States, your connection will be through and to servers located in the United States: 1) your orders placed through our Services will be fully processed in and shipped from the United States; and 2) all information you provide will be processed and maintained in our web servers and internal systems located within the United States. By using the Services, you authorize the export of Personal Information to the United States and its storage and use, as specified above, when you provide such information to us. This privacy policy and our legal obligations are subject to the laws of the State of New York and the United States, regardless of the location of any user of the Services. Any claims or complaints must be filed in the State of New York in the United States.

**Policies for Children Under the Age of 13.**

The Services are not directed to children under the age of 13.  To register for a user account for the Services, you must be 13 years of age or older.  You may not register for a user account for the Services if you are under 13 years of age. 

Note to Parents: MLG does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13, and please instruct your children to never provide personal information on this Website or any other web site without your permission.  The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”) requires web sites that know that visitors to their site may be under the age of 13 to follow specific Federal Trade Commission rules.  In our attempt to fully comply with these rules, we would like you to know that, MLG will not knowingly collect or solicit any personally identifiable offline contact information or personal online contact information from children under the age of 13. No information should be submitted to the Services by children under 13 years of age.

If you have concerns about the Services, wish to find out if your child is a member or has registered for one our Services, or wish to cancel your child's membership, please contact us at remove@mlgpro.com. If you believe that your child under 13 has gained access to our Services, please contact us at [parents@mlgpro.com](mailto:parents@mlgpro.com).

**Transfer of Business Assets.**  
The Personal Information you provide is considered a company asset and may be included among transferred assets if Major League Gaming, any or all of its subsidiaries or affiliates or any of their assets is ever acquired by or merged with those of a third party.

**Changes to this Policy.**  
Because our business needs may change over time, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this privacy policy at any time. Such changes, modifications, additions or deletions will be effective immediately upon notice thereof, which may be given by means including, but not limited to, posting on the Website, or by electronic or conventional mail, or by any other means by which you obtain notice thereof. Any use of the Services by you after such notice will be deemed to constitute your acceptance of such changes, modifications, additions or deletions.  If any modification, change, addition or change to these terms and conditions are not acceptable to you, your only recourse is to refrain from using and accessing the Services.

**How To Unsubscribe.**

All unsubscribe requests should be sent to us at remove@mlgpro.com and we will process your request within a reasonable time after receipt. However, we are not responsible for removing your Personal Information from lists of any third parties that have previously been provided your information in accordance with this policy. 

**Services Terms of Use.**

Use of the Services, including this Website, is governed by and subject to the Major League Gaming [Terms of Use](https://accounts.majorleaguegaming.com/terms_of_service).  Your use, or access of the Services, constitutes your agreement to be bound by this privacy policy and the Major League Gaming Terms of Use. 

**How to Contact Us.**  
If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy you may [contact us](https://support.majorleaguegaming.com/) through the Website or write to the following address:  
Major League Gaming

3 Park Avenue, 32nd Floor  
New York, NY 10016  
Attn: Privacy

**United States of America:**   Our Services are maintained in the United States of America. By using the Services, you authorize the export of Personal Information to the USA and its storage and use as specified in this policy.

Effective Date: This privacy policy was last updated on January 25, 2013.

© 2013 Major League Gaming Inc.

Major League Gaming, MLG, the MLG logos, GameBattles, the GameBattles logo, GotFrag, and the GotFrag logo, are the exclusive properties of Major League Gaming Inc.
